Preliminary Inventory of the Lee Edwards Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Sound recordings (Box 1, 8-11, 152-153, 163, 213-221, 330)
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Goldwater on 18 Dec 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008007
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ron Crawford on 14 Jan 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008029
  - Lee Edwards interviews Tom Winter on 4 Feb 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008471
  - Sally Quinn interviews Barry Goldwater on the Tomorrow Show, sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 215)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008482
  - Lee Edwards interviews Charles Percy on 9 Dec 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008502
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dave Broder on 24 Aug 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008488
  - Lee Edwards interviews Donald Saltz on 1 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008492
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Crane on 26 Jan 1994, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008503
    This interview is about Barry Goldwater, the conservative movement, and libertarianism. Specific topics include nuclear weapons, Charles Murray and implications of race relations in peoples' perception of the Republican Party, health care reforms and the Heritage Foundation's mandate plan, Milton Friedman, F. A. Hayek, Ayn Rand, drug legalization, and running against JFK in 1964.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Frank Kovac via telephone on 13 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008496
  - Lee Edwards interviews James Harff on 2 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008493
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jerry Smith on 1 Oct 1992, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008497
  - Lee Edwards interviews Joanne Goldwater on 6 Jan 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008486
  - Lee Edwards interviews John H. Buchanan, Jr. on 3 Sep 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008495
  - Lee Edwards interviews Sally Quinn via telephone on 29 Oct 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008500
  - Lee Edwards interviews Sam Hay via telephone on 24 Aug 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 216)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008491
  - Eleanor Quinn sound recording from 2 Oct 1989, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008943
  - Lee Edwards interviews Carolyn Judd on 30 Sep 1989, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008939
  - Lee Edwards interviews Leonard Unger on 28 Jul 1988, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008938
    This interview is about Walter Judd.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Miriam Judd on 23 October 1986, 4 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009131
    This interview is about Walter Judd's time in the United States Congress.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter and Miriam Judd on 19 February 1988, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009191
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 10 Feb 1988, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009146
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 11 Sep 1987, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009141
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 12 Jan 1988, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009145
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 13 April 1988, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009193
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 19 March 1988, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009192
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 21 February 1987, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009136
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 21 Jun 1989, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008947
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 22 February 1987, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009135
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 22 May 1985, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008952
    Edwards interviews Judd as research for his dissertation on the "Do Nothing" 80th Congress.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 24 Oct 1988, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008944
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 30 Dec 1987, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009142
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 30 May 1987 and Ronald Reagan on 10 February 1975, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009140
    Part 1-3: Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd, 30 May 1987
    Part 4: Lee Edwards interviews Ronald Reagan, 10 February 1975.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 7 Nov 1981, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008950
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 7 Nov 1988, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008946
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter H. Judd on 9 Nov 1985, 2 sound cassettes (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008953
  - Walter H. Judd at the Anti-Communist School in 1966, sound recording, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008936
  - Walter H. Judd sound recording from 8 July 1986, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009130
  - Walter H. Judd speech on 18 Jul 1989, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008949
  - Walter H. Judd speech: Hollywood's Answer to Communism, 1 sound cassette (Box 217)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008935
  - Lee Edwards interviews Adam Meyerson on 15 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009210
  - Lee Edwards interviews Adam Meyerson on 6 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009197
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bridgett Wagner on 20 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009363
    This interview is about the Heritage Foundation.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dave Mason on 7 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009202
  - Lee Edwards interviews Herb Berkowitz on 8 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009203
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Von Kannon on 8 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009207
  - Lee Edwards interviews Kim Holmes on 8 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009206
  - Lee Edwards interviews Lew Gayner on 13 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009209
  - Lee Edwards interviews Phil Truluck on 13 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009359
  - Lee Edwards interviews Phil Truluck on 6 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009198
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Odernatt on 15 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009360
  - Lee Edwards interviews Stuart Butler on 7 March 1996, 1 sound cassette (Box 218)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009201
  - Lee Edwards interviews Andy Toncic on 12 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008015
    Lee Edwards interviews Andy Toncic about his time as dean at Grove City College and his student career at the college.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Andy Walters on 13 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008020
    This interview is about Grove City College, athletics on campus, and Title IX.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Becky Gilger on 11 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008011
    This interview is about Gilger's grandfather and Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Brad Wilson on 17 Nov 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008784
    Lee Edwards interviews Brad Wilson, a political philosopher, about higher education in America during his research for his book on Grove City College. Wilson argues many of the problems of colleges and universities in 1998 are a result of the changes of the 1960s and a resulting politicization of the classroom. The interview has very little to do with Grove City College itself.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bruce Ketler on 19 Nov 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008787
    Lee Edwards interviews Bruce Ketler about Grove City College and Ketler's grandfather, a past president of the college.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dale Boune on 13 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008022
    This interview concerns Presbyterianism, Grove City College, and religious life on campus.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dave Dayton on 6 Mar 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008003
    This interview concerns Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews David Lascell on 10 Nov 1998, 3.0 sound microcassettes (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008778
    Edwards interviews Lascell at length about legal issues and Grove City College, including the Supreme Court case involving Title IX and its implications. In the process, the conversation also briefly touches on (a) the administration of the college, (b) fraternities at Grove City and elsewhere, (c) antitrust suit against Kodak, and (d) Hillsdale College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Diane Grundy on 14 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008025
    This interview is about Grove City College, especially presidents and students thereof.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Dick Morlidge on 22 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008043
    This interview is about Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Arnold on 13 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008016
    This interview concerns music and arts at Grove City College, especially the band program.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Elizabeth Nixon on 24 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008031
    Nixon, a sophomore student and child of two professors, gives her thoughts on Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Garth Runun on 15 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008027
    This interview is about Grove City College. Runun concentrates on the Christian aspect of the College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Hans Sennholz on 5 Mar 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008001
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jack Behringer on 8 May 1998, 2.0 sound microcassettes (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008006
    This interview concerns Grove City College, American higher education, and collegiate athletics. He sees the role of athletics as integral to Grove City's mission.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jeff Wallin in May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008005
    This interview concerns Grove City College and American higher education.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Joe Goncz on 11 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008010
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Moore on 24 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008030
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Morer on 5 Mar 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008000
    Lee Edwards interviews Morer about Grove City College, dating from his grandfather's involvement to his children's.
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Sparks on 13 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008019
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Van Tyl on 12 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008013
  - Lee Edwards interviews Karen Swenson on 13 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008023
    This interview concerns Grove City Campus, especially the experience for female students.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Kim Stetson on 25 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008036
    This interview is about Grove City College, Stetson's experiences as a student, and her work on the campus newspaper.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Laura Conner on 24 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008028
    Conner, a sophomore marketing major and former music business major, gives her thoughts on Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Matthew Donnelly on 25 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008033
    Donnelly, a fraternity member at Grove City College offers his thoughts about the Greek system at the college. This interview starts about 10:30 into part 1.
    Also on the tape is an interview, with a man possibly named Jeff, about admissions to the college. This secondary program is found both before and after the Donnelly interview.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Michael Coulter on 22 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008038
  - Lee Edwards interviews Nancy Paxton on 11 May 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008008
    This interview is about Grove City College. Among the topics covered include: Paxton's interest in missionary work (which Edwards compares to Walter Judd), her student career at the college, her time as Dean of Students, various presidents of the College, changes in students of the years, sororities/fraternities, minorities on campus, roommate matching, and financial aid.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Bonacelli on 3 Nov 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008047
    Bonacelli recalls his time as a professor at Grove City College. He criticizes the college on several aspects, but spends a considerable amount of time discussing how the College's policies were antagonistic to his financial and career goals.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Kengor on 22 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008039
    Paul Kengor, professor of political science, gives his thoughts on Grove City College. He says it was his dream to teach at the college.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Robert Smith on 5 Mar 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008002
    This interview concerns Grove City College and Smith's work as the registrar.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ross Foster, 2.0 sound microcassettes (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007989
    Lee Edwards interviews Ross Foster about Foster's time at Grove City College, both as a professor and as a dean. Foster concentrates on how he and Pew turned the school around, bringing it back to its Christian roots. He argues the college is attractive as it offers a quality education at an affordable price and Christian values. He expands upon several specific reforms he made as dean and problems he observed as a professor.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ruth and Bill Mills on 20 Nov 1998, 2.0 sound microcassettes (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008789
    Ruth outlines the experiences of her and her family, over generations, with Grove City College.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Scott Peroell on 19 Nov 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008788
  - Lee Edwards interviews Steve Balch on 16 Nov 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008783
  - Lee Edwards interviews Tony Hall on 24 Aug 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0007942
    This interview concerns Hall's experience as a student at Grove City College. Edwards interviews her at a time when she is actively seeking to transfer to a different school for academic reasons.
    Among her criticisms of the academics, she does not believe the professors are knowledgeable of the field post-their-higher-education, citing the lack of professor requirement to publish. She believes the education is overly biased against leftism--an inverse of the contemporary stereotype of higher education. She finds the library woefully inadequate, citing her need to drive for two hours out-of-state to do her research.
    Other topics include a campus-wide sexism against women both from professors and from students of both genders, students that are not Christian or heterosexual, the dorms, alcohol on campus, the transferring process, and the lack of female role models on campus.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Walter Ransom on 24 Sep 1998, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 219)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008035
  - Ben Hart sound recording from 8 Oct 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008852
  - Grace-Marie Arnett sound recording from 7 Oct 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008849
  - Lee Edwards interviews Bruce Chapman on 27 May 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008808
  - Lee Edwards interviews Chas Heathaly on 19 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008834
  - Lee Edwards interviews Chas Kesler on 19 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008835
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Crane on 24 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008795
    This interview is about think tanks, the work of the Cato Institute and Heritage Foundation, conservatism, and libertarianism.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Ed Noble on 13 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008794
  - Lee Edwards interviews Edwin J. Feulner on 27 Sep 1996, 2.0 sound microcassettes (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008847
  - Lee Edwards interviews Gerald A. Dorfman on 23 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008838
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation, the Hoover Institution, think tanks in general, and the conservative movement.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Gordon Jones on 30 May 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008810
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation and Jones' time there.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jack Kemp on 6 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008820
  - Lee Edwards interviews Jim Peyser on 26 May 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008807
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Cooper on 28 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008804
  - Lee Edwards interviews John Von Kannon on 10 Sep 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008839
  - Lee Edwards interviews Joseph Coors on 18 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008831
  - Lee Edwards interviews Lenore Ealy on 27 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008798
  - Lee Edwards interviews Martin Anderson on 5 Aug 1997, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008877
    This interview is about the conservative movement of the 20th century.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Michael Barone on 26 Jul 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008814
  - Lee Edwards interviews Midge Decter on 13 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008790
  - Lee Edwards interviews Mike Franc on 16 Dec 1997, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008844
  - Lee Edwards interviews Mike Joyce on 13 Apr 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008796
    This interview concerns the Heritage Foundation and conservatism.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich on 3 Dec 1997, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008878
    Lee Edwards interviews Paul Weyrich about the conservative movement of the 20th century, with an emphasis on Newt Gingrich, both his rise to and term as Speaker of the House.
    Also on the tape is an unidentified interview with, what sounds like, an elderly gentleman. He and Edwards discuss the Hoover Institution.
  - Lee Edwards interviews Richard Larry on 1 Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008815
  - Lee Edwards interviews T. Kenneth Cribb, Jr., on 23 Nov 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008874
    This interview is about the Heritage Foundation and its impact on the conservative movement and the ISI. In the process, he often delves into stories of the time he spent in the Reagan administration, including, but not limited to, the Iran-Contra affair.
  - Lee Edwards sound recording, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008819
    This microcassette is labeled as an interview with Jack Kemp, however, the recording is simply Edwards saying "Good morning" with nothing else on the tape.
  - Matt Spalding sound recording from 19 Sep 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008843
  - Sound recording of a conversation between Lee Edwards and Edwin J. Feulner, Jr., on 23 Jan 1997, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008876
    This is about Edwards' book on the Heritage Foundation. It sounds like they are going over sections of the book Feulner would like to see changed.
  - Sound recording of a conversation between Lee Edwards and Stuart Butler on 26 Feb 1997, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008875
    This conversation is about the Heritage Foundation and its relationship with the politics and issues of the 1980s and 1990s, particularly healthcare reform.
  - Steve Forbes, Dick Armey, and Dan Lungren sound recordings from Aug 1996, 1.0 sound microcassette (Box 220)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0008822
    Part 1: Steve Forbes, 12 Aug 1996
    Part 2: Dick Armey, Dan Lungren, 15 Aug 1996
  - Lee Edwards interviews Barry Goldwater in February 1991, 1 sound cassette (Box 221)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009292
  - Lee Edwards interviews Barry Goldwater, Jr., on 27 April 1993, 1 sound cassette (Box 221)
    Use copy reference number: 2010c14_a_0009338
    Edwards conducted this interview by telephone.